【The fate that cannot be liberated】
[해방될 수 없는 운명]
[Episode 2]
[2화]
【Astrology Center】
【점성술 센터】
please.
제발.
After you.
당신 후.
【Astrology Center】
【점성술 센터】
Miss, please.
아가씨, 제발요.
What do the numbers in this passage mean?
이 구절에 나오는 숫자는 무엇을 의미하나요?
Today our young master
오늘은 우리 젊은 스승님
some of you will be chosen
너희 중 일부는 선택될 것이다
and divines for whomever he chooses .
그리고 그가 선택한 사람을 위해 점을 칩니다 .
One number per person. Keep it safe.
1인당 하나의 번호입니다. 안전을 유지해라.
So many people, there is a chance to be called
사람이 너무 많아서 부를 기회가 있어요
They must be small, right?
분명 작겠죠?
When the sun rises from the earth,
태양이 땅에서 떠오를 때,
Affects all sentient beings.
모든 지각 있는 존재에게 영향을 미칩니다.
[Star Pavilion] All living beings are prosperous.
[스타 파빌리온] 모든 생명체는 번영합니다.
The sun sets on the earth.
태양이 지구에 집니다.
We enter the world of Yin.
우리는 음의 세계로 들어갑니다.
In autumn, yin and yang compete.
가을에는 음과 양이 경쟁합니다.
In winter, Yang Qi is hidden in stronger Yin Qi.
겨울에는 양기가 더 강한 음기에 숨어 ​​있습니다.
When the long night ends, the sun rises again.
긴 밤이 끝나면 다시 해가 뜬다.
The south represents light.
남쪽은 빛을 상징한다.
Everything is visible.
모든 것이 보입니다.
She is the embodiment of the South.
그녀는 남부의 화신입니다.
Excellent!
훌륭한!
touching.
감동.
- Do you understand it? - Missed.
- 이해가 되시나요? - 놓쳤어요.
Are you here because of Star Catcher?
스타캐처 때문에 오셨나요?
as you know?
아시다시피?
girls who come here
여기 오는 여자들
10 out of 10
10점 만점에 10점
They are waiting for him here.
그들은 여기서 그를 기다리고 있습니다.
I assume you have this flyer too, don't you?
당신도 이 전단지를 갖고 있는 것 같은데요, 그렇죠?
Let me tell you, the most popular image of the capital city
수도의 가장 대중적인 이미지를 알려드릴게요
I gave it to you.
나는 그것을 당신에게 주었다.
a woman like you
너 같은 여자
is their favorite.
그들이 가장 좋아하는 것입니다.
women like me
나 같은 여자들
hatred.
증오.
You have high standards.
당신은 높은 기준을 가지고 있습니다.
Long life, happiness and joy.
장수, 행복과 기쁨.
Excellent.
훌륭한.
This is my unpublished work.
저의 미발표 작품입니다.
Very collectible.
매우 소장 가치가 있습니다.
You will definitely thank me after reading it.
읽고 나면 분명 나에게 감사할 것이다.
Thank you now.
이제 감사합니다.
-Are you disparaging my painting skills? - Never.
- 내 그림 실력을 폄하하는 겁니까? - 절대.
I gave it to you for free, but you refused.
무료로 드렸는데 거절하셨어요.
As Mr. Xiaoyao, I am the best painter.
샤오야오 씨로서 저는 최고의 화가입니다.
- But I feel humiliated. - shut up!
- 하지만 모욕감을 느꼈어요. - 입 다물어!
The ninth prophecy is that there will be no war on the border.
아홉 번째 예언은 국경에서는 전쟁이 없을 것이라는 것입니다.
The tenth hexagram means peace and prosperity for the country and the people.
열 번째 육각형은 국가와 국민의 평화와 번영을 의미합니다.
Excellent.
훌륭한.
- what is that? -you all think
- 저게 뭐에요? -다들 그렇게 생각하지
que a Rong Yu
유 롱(Rong Yu)이요
Is he a fairy?
그는 요정인가요?
Clear.
분명한.
I believe he will eat.
나는 그가 먹을 것이라고 믿습니다.
He Himself chooses the gods.
그 자신이 신들을 선택합니다.
- I suggest you change your career tomorrow. - Why?
- 내일 직업을 바꾸는 것이 좋습니다. - 왜?
Because today I will make him the butt of a joke.
오늘은 내가 그 사람을 농담거리로 만들 것이기 ​​때문이다.
The astrology center will send the results to your home tomorrow.
점성술 센터에서는 내일 집으로 결과를 보낼 것입니다.
Why do we have to wait until tomorrow?
왜 우리는 내일까지 기다려야 합니까?
What?
무엇?
Who is that? what is she doing?
그 사람은 누구입니까? 그녀가 무엇을하고 있니?
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
- Where is that person? - Yes.
- 그 사람은 어디에 있나요? - 예.
I've never seen him before.
나는 그를 본 적이 없습니다.
Could it be that the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion cannot
혹시 흥향각의 젊은 스승은 그럴 수 없 겠는가?
Need someone else?
다른 사람이 필요합니까?
or maybe
아니면 아마도
You need time to investigate them
조사할 시간이 필요해요
Forge and invent some riddles?
수수께끼를 만들고 발명해 볼까요?
Who are you and why are you making all this fuss?
당신은 누구이며 왜 이렇게 소란을 피우는 걸까요?
do not be afraid.
두려워 하지마.
Why be afraid?
왜 두려워합니까?
I did nothing.
나는 아무것도 하지 않았다.
what is she doing?
그녀가 무엇을하고 있니?
Could it be that Jialin people
혹시 Jialin 사람들이 그럴까요?
Can't you speak publicly these days?
요즘 공개적으로 말할 수 없나요?
What a disappointment.
정말 실망 스럽습니다.
all good.
문제 없다.
Everyone is back.
모두가 돌아 왔습니다.
miss.
놓치다.
Waiting for tomorrow doesn't suit me,
내일을 기다리는 건 나에겐 어울리지 않아
someone's fate, fortune, disaster
누군가의 운명, 행운, 재난
It should only be known to that person.
그 사람만 알아야 해요.
If I can't reveal it publicly
공개적으로 밝힐 수 없다면
Why is everyone sitting here for nothing?
왜 다들 괜히 여기에 앉아 있는 걸까요?
Who says no one wants to
아무도 원하지 않는다고 누가 말하던가
Reveal your riddle to everyone?
수수께끼를 모두에게 공개하시겠습니까?
I want everyone to
모두가 그랬으면 좋겠어
Look at my fate.
내 운명을보세요.
What? What's wrong?
무엇? 뭐가 문제 야?
I learned that the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion
나는 Xingxiang Pavilion의 젊은 스승이
Very talented.
매우 재능있는.
stop hiding
그만 숨으세요
and tell me my destiny
그리고 내 운명을 말해줘
Show it to everyone.
모두에게 보여주세요.
- about what? - No guesswork if you are not selected.
- 뭐에 대해서요? - 선정되지 않은 경우에는 추측할 수 없습니다.
this is the rule
이것이 규칙이다
Annual Astrology Festival.
연례 점성술 축제.
This cannot be broken with just one sentence.
이것은 한 문장만으로는 깨질 수 없습니다.
And if everyone
그리고 만약 모두가
Ask the young master
젊은 주인에게 물어보세요
Practicing divination?
점술을 연습하시나요?
Exactly.
정확히.
- Why does she need that? - and.
- 그게 왜 필요한데? - 그리고.
She doesn't even know the rules.
그녀는 규칙조차 모릅니다.
Simple.
단순한.
- You, how could you do this? - How could she do this?
- 너, 어떻게 이럴 수가 있지? - 어떻게 이런 일을 할 수 있지?
- She's a troublemaker. - Did she just catch them?
- 말썽꾸러기야. - 방금 잡았나요?
Leave this outside the rules.
이것을 규칙 외부에 두십시오.
- What? - I follow the rules.
- 무엇? - 나는 규칙을 따른다.
No. 48.
48호.
No. 48, is anyone there?
48번, 거기 누구 없어요?
- who is it? - No. 48. Not us, right?
- 누구예요? - 48번. 우리는 아니죠?
Number 48, right? here.
48번이죠? 여기.
it's me. I can't believe I was chosen.
나야. 제가 선택됐다는 게 믿기지 않아요.
look at me.
날 봐.
Who is number 48?
48번은 누구야?
He, he, he, gemendo.
그, 그, 그, 게멘도.
very good.
매우 좋은.
it's me.
나야.
They groaned.
그들은 신음했다.
I just follow the rules, don't I?
나는 단지 규칙을 따를 뿐이죠, 그렇죠?
all good. you did it!
문제 없다. 훌륭해!
And me?
그리고 나?
Who else wants to claim 48?
또 누가 48세를 주장하고 싶나요?
If so, please move forward.
그렇다면 앞으로 나아가시기 바랍니다.
It seems I am the chosen one.
아무래도 나는 선택받은 자인 것 같다.
So please, Master.
그러니 부탁드립니다, 스승님.
Miss He, what do you want to diagnose?
Miss He, 무엇을 진단하고 싶나요?
This is my wedding destination.
이곳은 나의 결혼식 목적지입니다.
Okay, please.
알았어, 제발.
Madam, please tell us your date of birth.
부인, 생년월일을 알려주세요.
In the sixth year of Zhenyuan,
진원 6년에,
December 22nd.
12월 22일.
There's another knock on the door. She's always like this.
또 문을 두드리는 소리가 난다. 그녀는 항상 이렇습니다.
Look at her.
그녀를 봐.
Why didn't you say anything?
왜 아무 말도 하지 않았나요?
What's the prognosis?
예상은 어떻습니까?
Is it necessary to read so much?
꼭 그렇게 많이 읽어야 하나요?
Can not you see?
볼 수 없나요?
The proficiency level of the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion
싱샹정 젊은 스승의 숙련도
more or less.
다소간.
What is the difference between you and those who are chasing fame and wealth ?
명예와 부를 쫓는 사람들과 당신의 차이점은 무엇입니까 ?
This makes me question the quality of your astrology studio.
이것은 당신의 점성술 스튜디오의 품질에 의문을 제기하게 만듭니다.
Don't say stupid things.
어리석은 말을하지 마십시오.
What did I say wrong?
내가 뭘 잘못 말했나요?
I've seen the results.
나는 결과를 보았다.
Although,
하지만,
Multiple sclerosis. He, can you let me confirm again?
다발성 경화증. 그 사람, 다시 확인해 주시겠어요?
As?
처럼?
I'm so self-righteous
난 너무 독선적이야
But miss. Can he get close to the tent?
하지만 그리워요. 텐트에 가까이 다가갈 수 있나요?
Let me touch the top of your head?
머리 꼭대기 좀 만져볼까?
Clear.
분명한.
Why do I smell Phalaenopsis?
호접란 냄새는 왜 나는 걸까요?
forget.
잊다.
if you tell the truth
당신이 진실을 말한다면
The fate of our marriage was not good;
우리 결혼의 운명은 좋지 않았다.
I'll let her go.
나는 그녀를 보내줄 것이다.
if you dare to use me
감히 나를 이용하려 한다면
Say something nice,
좋은 말 좀 해주세요,
I will make you a star-catching master
너를 별 잡는 달인으로 만들어줄게
Falling apart today.
오늘 무너지고 있습니다.
Silta. he.
실타. 그.
sorry.
죄송합니다.
Rong Yu,
유 롱,
you know me.
당신은 나를 알고 있습니다.
Although we haven't officially met yet,
아직 정식으로 만난 적은 없지만,
I think you should know
내 생각엔 네가 알아야 할 것 같아
Why am I here.
내가 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Run quickly.
빨리 달려.
here. hide.
여기. 숨다.
good life.
좋은 인생.
Come, Prince Zheng
오세요, 정 왕자님
Let's get out of here.
여기서 나가자.
He made a big fuss in the capital,
그는 수도에서 큰 소란을 일으켰고,
——Don’t you know there is a He family? -Heshan.
——당신은 그 가족이 있다는 것을 모르십니까? -허샨.
Master.
주인.
Master, look.
선생님, 보세요.
- let's break up. - Yes.
- 헤어지자. - 예.
【Astrology Center】
【점성술 센터】
Pessigam separated.
페시감이 분리되었습니다.
What about the horse?
말은 어떻습니까?
- Who are you? ——He family, from the capital.
- 누구세요? ——그 가족, 수도 출신.
How dare you be so presumptuous?
어떻게 감히 그렇게 주제넘게 굴 수 있나요?
nonsense.
무의미한 말.
Bro, wait, wait.
형, 잠깐만요.
Don't go away now.
지금은 떠나지 마세요.
You are that man!
당신이 그 사람이에요!
I know.
알아요.
Although Xingxiang Pavilion is very famous, there,
Xingxiang Pavilion 은 매우 유명하지만,
Shangzhou’s sister
상저우의 여동생
It's so nice and virtuous.
너무 착하고 고결해요.
How could you change your loyalties so quickly?
어떻게 당신의 충성심을 그렇게 빨리 바꿀 수 있었습니까?
Where is your conscience?
당신의 양심은 어디에 있습니까?
Sister, do you still remember our agreement yesterday?
언니, 어제 우리가 약속한 걸 아직도 기억하시나요?
Next time we meet, you should.
다음에 만나면 꼭 해야지.
Make up for the massage you deserve.
당신에게 합당한 마사지를 보충하십시오.
Did something happen to my sister?
내 여동생에게 무슨 일이라도 생긴 걸까?
No.
아니요.
I know. You have no heart.
알아요. 당신은 마음이 없습니다.
Silta. he.
실타. 그.
- You you you - take them with you.
- 너 너 너 - 가져가세요.
I don't even want to talk to you.
나는 당신과 이야기하고 싶지도 않습니다.
Take your broken sword.
부러진 검을 가져가세요.
You are afraid of me.
당신은 나를 두려워합니다.
that's right.
좋아요.
as you can see today
오늘 보시다시피
and have heard in the past:
과거에 다음과 같은 말을 들었습니다.
I, He Jiuling, am a fierce general.
나 허구령은 맹렬한 장군이다.
I have a bad temper and am not very kind.
나는 성격이 나쁘고 그다지 친절하지 않습니다.
So, what do you think of the fate of our marriage?
그렇다면 우리 결혼의 운명은 어떻게 될까요?
groom.
신랑.
Silta. Hey,
실타. 여기요,
Why do you always abuse my young master?
왜 항상 내 젊은 스승님을 학대하시나요?
always?
언제나?
You've adapted well to your new owner, haven't you?
새 주인에게 잘 적응했지요?
Why did I bully him?
내가 왜 그를 괴롭혔나요?
I didn't even touch it.
나는 그것을 만지지도 않았다.
Since I started practicing martial arts, how many young people have I hurt?
무술을 시작한 이래로 나는 얼마나 많은 젊은이들에게 상처를 입혔습니까?
There can be a queue of more than 800 meters.
800m 이상의 대기열이 있을 수 있습니다.
What is your young master's position?
젊은 스승님의 직위는 무엇입니까?
also,
또한,
I guard the arrow for you,
나는 당신을 위해 화살을 지키고,
I'll also help you catch the bad guys.
나쁜 놈들을 잡는 것도 도와줄게.
Have you forgotten everything?
다 잊으셨나요?
This agenda
이 의제
He saved me when the lady was left behind.
그 여자가 남겨졌을 때 그는 나를 구해줬어요.
If you keep it with you,
가지고 다니면,
It must be very valuable.
그것은 매우 가치 있는 일임에 틀림없다.
Silta. he.
실타. 그.
How can such a vulgar pamphlet be used?
이렇게 저속한 팜플렛을 어떻게 사용할 수 있습니까?
Fantasy about my young master?
내 젊은 스승에 대한 환상이요?
- No! ——Stay away from the young master.
- 아니요! ——젊은 스승에게서 멀어지세요.
Even if it can be done in the future
앞으로도 그럴 수 있다고 해도
Not today.
오늘 말고.
No, someone gave it to me for free.
아니요, 누군가가 무료로 제공했습니다.
It's not free.
그것은 무료가 아닙니다.
They forced me to use it.
그들은 나에게 그것을 사용하도록 강요했습니다.
Anyway, I don't see any page.
어쨌든 페이지가 보이지 않네요.
Don't get me wrong.
오해하지 마세요.
I see.
알겠어요.
great.
엄청난.
If it's not precious, why are you carrying it?
소중하지도 않다면 왜 들고 다니나요?
I've already said it.
나는 이미 그것을 말했다.
Now,
지금,
Someone put it on me in the hallway.
누군가 복도에서 나에게 그것을 올려 놓았습니다.
What a coincidence.
이런 우연이.
- You... - Flatten!
- 너... - 납작하게!
Anyway, I'll find a place to burn it later.
어쨌든 나중에 태울 곳을 찾아봐야겠습니다.
keep Calm.
침착함을 유지하세요.
As for marriage,
결혼에 관해서는,
If you find it difficult to speak,
말하기 어려우시다면,
I see.
알겠어요.
We seemed to be on the same page.
우리는 같은 페이지에있는 것 같았습니다.
I'll wait for you at my house.
우리 집에서 기다릴게요.
The sooner we address this issue, the better. You need to hurry up.
이 문제는 빨리 해결할수록 좋습니다. 서둘러야 해요.
It has been sent to the Ministry of Punishment.
형벌부로 보냈습니다.
my brother works there
내 동생이 거기서 일해
and will look into it for you.
그리고 당신을 위해 그것을 조사할 것입니다.
Let's break up here. I'm going home first.
여기서 헤어지자 나 먼저 집에 갈 거야.
His wound was still bleeding.
그의 상처에는 아직도 피가 흐르고 있었다.
I'll be scared if this continues.
계속 이러면 겁날 것 같아요.
But all the medical clinics around
하지만 주변의 모든 진료소는
Will be investigated by government soldiers.
정부군이 조사할 예정이다.
Let's consider another solution.
다른 해결책을 고려해 봅시다.
Rong Yu.
유 롱.
I must kill him.
나는 그를 죽여야만 한다.
Master.
주인.
He looked worried.
그는 걱정스러운 표정을 지었다.
Multiple sclerosis. Isn't he very good?
다발성 경화증. 그 사람 정말 좋은 사람 아닌가요?
I didn't see her marital destiny.
나는 그녀의 결혼 운명을 보지 못했습니다.
why not?
왜 안 돼?
After all, she is your fiancée, isn't she?
결국, 그녀는 당신의 약혼자죠, 그렇죠?
because i saw
내가 봤으니까
Four years later,
4년 후,
She will die in Jialin.
그녀는 Jialin에서 죽을 것이다.
How can this be?
어떻게 이럴 수있어?
When the previous owner arranged the wedding,
전 주인이 결혼식을 주선했을 때,
He doesn't understand?
그 사람은 이해 못해요?
Her fate is strange.
그녀의 운명은 이상합니다.
It's just that they couldn't find it on her birthday, which is normal.
단지 그녀의 생일에 그것을 찾을 수 없다는 것이 정상입니다.
Even I could only vaguely discern it.
나조차도 어렴풋이 알 수 있을 뿐이었다.
If Miss He only has four years left to live,
미스 헤의 수명이 4년밖에 남지 않았다면,
Master, isn't it?
선생님, 그렇죠?
Like a wizard,
마법사처럼,
we see signs
우리는 징후를 본다
and images
및 이미지
Not to fulfill destiny
운명을 이루기 위해서가 아니라
but fight another way
하지만 다른 방식으로 싸워라
Get rid of this fate.
이 운명을 제거하십시오.
The children of the aristocracy were born into poverty.
귀족의 자녀들은 가난하게 태어났습니다.
Patients must fight to survive.
환자들은 생존을 위해 싸워야 합니다.
In view of extreme circumstances,
극단적인 상황을 고려하여,
They need to endure a lot of pain to survive.
그들은 살아남기 위해 많은 고통을 견뎌야 합니다.
people are not
사람들은 그렇지 않다
Have you been fighting against your destiny all your life?
당신은 평생 동안 운명에 맞서 싸워왔나요?
Master,
주인,
Exactly. I'm very happy.
정확히. 나는 매우 행복 해요.
Exactly.
정확히.
Do you understand it? I'm very happy.
이해가 되시나요? 나는 매우 행복 해요.
Even though the journey is difficult,
여행이 힘들어도
I must change her fate
나는 그녀의 운명을 바꿔야 한다
Against nature.
자연에 반대합니다.
Jiuling, it looks like you've caused a stir.
Jiuling, 당신이 파문을 일으킨 것 같습니다.
Yesterday at the Astrology Festival.
어제 점성술 축제에서.
No wonder Rong Mansion sent someone here early in the morning.
Rong Mansion이 이른 아침에 누군가를 여기로 보낸 것도 당연합니다 .
It can't wait.
기다릴 수 없습니다.
- Serious? ——Yes, as soon as Mr. Rong arrives,
- 심각한? ——네, 롱 씨가 도착하자마자
I'll run to call you.
달려가서 전화할게요.
Yesterday was worth grabbing.
어제는 잡을 가치가 있었습니다.
Get up and get dressed.
일어나서 옷을 입으세요.
Rong Yu looks like a weakling
유용준은 약해 보이는데
But it works quickly.
하지만 빨리 작동합니다.
Yes, after all, you are Rong Yu’s fiancée
네, 결국 당신은 Rong Yu의 약혼자입니다
More than ten years.
10년 이상.
Mr. Rong should compensate more.
Rong 씨는 더 많은 보상을 해야 합니다.
We can't lose.
우리는 질 수 없습니다.
- quickly. - correct.
- 빠르게. - 옳은.
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
How did this happen?
어떻게 이런일이 일어 났습니까?
A Rong Yu se feriu?
Rong Yu se feriu?
Fortunately, Rong Yu was not injured.
다행히 유용주는 부상을 입지 않았다.
but i heard
하지만 난 들었어
The Cheng family wants revenge.
쳉 가족은 복수를 원한다.
Are you talking about Chengji?
청지(Chengji)를 말하는 건가요?
brazen.
단단한.
This is a family of thieves and prostitutes.
이것은 도둑과 매춘부의 가족입니다.
If Rong Yu hadn't discovered
유용우가 발견하지 못했다면
The location of the 30 million silver emergency fund,
3천만은 긴급자금의 위치는,
I'm afraid the Cheng family
Cheng 가족이 두렵습니다.
Rumors will still be spread.
소문은 계속 퍼질 것입니다.
Talking about the Silver Caravan
실버 캐러밴에 대해 이야기하기
Washed away by floods.
홍수로 씻겨 나갔습니다.
They destroyed the victims' money
그들은 피해자의 돈을 파괴했습니다
Carrying the emperor on his back.
황제를 등에 업고.
it's a huge shame
정말 부끄러운 일이야
Punish them for their hard work at the border.
국경에서 열심히 일한 그들을 처벌하십시오.
They dared to come back from the northwest to take revenge.
그들은 복수를 위해 감히 북서쪽에서 돌아왔습니다.
recently...
최근...
Even mice dare to challenge cats.
쥐조차도 감히 고양이에게 도전합니다.
If it weren't for the emperor's mercy
황제의 자비가 아니었다면
There won't be anything like yesterday.
어제 같은 일은 없을 거예요.
Something important happened yesterday.
어제 중요한 일이 일어났습니다.
I wish I could go with you.
당신과 함께 갈 수 있으면 좋겠어요.
Today, I brought some gifts to express my gratitude.
오늘은 감사의 마음을 표현하기 위해 몇 가지 선물을 가져왔습니다 .
If he hadn't been beaten
만일 그 사람이 구타를 당하지 않았다면
Those people had already killed Rong Yu
그 사람들은 이미 용우를 죽였어
and escaped without a trace.
그리고 흔적도 없이 탈출했다.
I can't stay here
난 여기 있을 수 없어
And talk calmly.
그리고 침착하게 이야기하세요.
wrinkle
멋진 생각
Indeed, she is a blessed girl.
실제로 그녀는 축복받은 소녀입니다.
She is a lucky girl.
그녀는 운이 좋은 소녀입니다.
But I'm a little confused.
하지만 조금 혼란스러워요.
I heard that everyone is riding a Rong Yu horse
모두가 용우 말을 타고 있다고 들었습니다
Almost ran off the bridge
거의 다리에서 도망칠 뻔했어
But the horse fell.
그러나 말이 떨어졌다.
I must say
꼭 말해야겠습니다
A bit fishy.
약간 비린내.
it's me.
나야.
We have guests at home, why are you still here?
집에 손님이 있는데 왜 아직도 여기 계시나요?
I'm thinking about horses, right?
나는 말에 대해 생각하고 있는 거죠, 그렇죠?
I'm the one who designed it.
나는 그것을 디자인한 사람이다.
what have you done?
당신은 무엇을 했나요?
I achieved a small success.
나는 작은 성공을 거두었습니다.
I'm a little excited.
나는 조금 흥분된다.
Say it quickly.
빨리 말해보세요.
I have been insisting
나는 주장해왔다.
Give He Jiuling the medicine
He Jiuling에게 약을 줘
Every day, he is a war horse for Rongfu.
매일 그는 Rongfu의 군마입니다.
As a result, the horses become weak and lethargic.
결과적으로 말은 약해지고 무기력해집니다.
Fainted at the critical moment.
결정적인 순간에 기절했습니다.
That's true.
그것은 사실이다.
What do you feed your horse? explain.
말에게 무엇을 먹이나요? 설명하다.
I love you.
사랑해요.
General He, don't be angry.
장군님, 화내지 마세요.
- Are you crazy? - I'm going to take the spring exam, right?
- 제정신이에요? - 나 봄학기 시험 보러 가는 거 맞지?
I want someone to give me recognition for what I do.
나는 누군가가 내가 하는 일을 인정해 주기를 원합니다.
I think I appreciate the gift too little.
제가 선물을 너무 적게 준 것 같아요.
After lunch in the afternoon, I will send someone there.
오후 점심 식사 후에 사람을 그곳으로 보내겠습니다.
I don't deserve your praise.
나는 당신의 칭찬을받을 자격이 없습니다.
I really don't deserve it.
나는 정말로 그럴 자격이 없습니다.
Since we agreed
우리가 동의한 이후로
About important issues.
중요한 문제에 대해.
I am going home.
난 집에 갈거야.
Please take a look
이것을 봐주세요
On the engagement gift list.
약혼 선물 목록에.
Our astrology center will send them
우리 점성술 센터에서 보내드릴 거예요
When calculating the best day of the month.
달의 가장 좋은 날을 계산할 때.
What about the engagement day?
약혼식 날은 어떻습니까?
- You decide. - all good.
- 당신이 결정해요. - 문제 없다.
Isn't he here to fulfill the engagement?
그 사람은 약혼을 이행하기 위해 여기 온 게 아닌가요?
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
How messy your hair is!
머리가 얼마나 지저분한지!
what are you doing here? go.
여기서 뭐하는거야? 가다.
Volt.
볼트.
Teacher Rong, please forgive me for the way I educate my daughter.
롱 선생님, 제가 제 딸을 교육하는 방식을 용서해주세요 .
I am so embarrassed.
너무 부끄럽습니다.
A Rong Yu calculou
A Rong Yu 계산
And our astrological compatibility is not good either.
그리고 우리의 점성학적 호환성도 좋지 않습니다.
Father, I found you.
아버지, 찾았습니다.
- you! - We have to cancel the wedding!
- 너! - 결혼식을 취소해야 해요!
Rong Yu didn't tell me anything.
유용준은 나에게 아무 말도 하지 않았다.
He must have forgotten.
그 사람은 잊어버린 게 틀림없어요.
But if I tell you, it’s worth it too.
하지만 내가 말하면 그만한 가치가 있습니다.
Do you understand it?
이해가 되시나요?
what are you saying?
당신이 무슨 말을하는거야?
you.
너.
How dare you hide from me?
어떻게 감히 나에게서 숨어?
You are terrible.
넌 최악이야.
Today I will teach you a lesson
오늘은 내가 너에게 교훈을 주겠다.
You are rebellious!
당신은 반항적이에요!
- You will see! - General, don't act without thinking.
- 보게 될 거예요! - 장군님, 생각 없이 행동하지 마십시오.
If it is really Rong Yu's plan,
그것이 정말로 용우의 계획이라면,
He won't hide it from me.
그는 나에게 그것을 숨기지 않을 것입니다.
As for the general's visit this time , it was to discuss the wedding.
이번 장군님의 방문은 결혼식에 관해 논의하기 위해서였습니다.
he mentioned
그가 언급한
"That lady?" he asked fiercely yesterday.
"그 여자요?" 그는 어제 맹렬하게 물었다.
I didn't ask.
나는 묻지 않았다.
How can I get him to propose to her?
그 사람이 그녀에게 프로포즈하게 하려면 어떻게 해야 할까요?
As for marriage,
결혼에 관해서는,
If you find it difficult to speak,
말하기 어려우시다면,
I see.
알겠어요.
We seemed to be on the same page.
우리는 같은 페이지에있는 것 같았습니다.
I'll wait for you at my house.
우리 집에서 기다릴게요.
The sooner we address this issue, the better.
이 문제는 빨리 해결할수록 좋습니다.
You need to hurry up.
서둘러야 해요.
drug.
의약품.
A misunderstanding.
오해.
This must be a misunderstanding
이건 오해임에 틀림없어
Misunderstand?
오해?
He didn't lose, he saw everything
그는 진 게 아니라 모든 걸 봤어
Pretending to cause trouble at the Astrology Festival
점성술 축제에서 문제를 일으키는 척
To attract these killers
킬러들을 유인하기 위해
confusion
착란
and forget their own safety
자신의 안전을 잊어버리고
And save Rong Yu?
그리고 Rong Yu를 구할까요?
I think
제 생각에는
You care about him.
당신은 그 사람에 관심이 있습니다.
Miss He, don't worry.
Miss He님, 걱정하지 마세요.
I won't let Rong Yu hurt you.
나는 Rong Yu가 당신을 해치게 두지 않을 것입니다.
Mr. Rong, this is a huge misunderstanding.
롱 씨, 이것은 큰 오해입니다.
I didn't pretend to cause trouble.
나는 문제를 일으키는 척하지 않았습니다.
really good.
정말 좋다.
Congratulations.
축하해요.
still have a question.
아직 질문이 있습니다.
you are wearing
너는 입는 중이다
a capa da Rong Yu?
카파 다 롱 유?
- very good. - This cover
- 매우 좋은. - 이 표지
It is made from the fur of the snowy mountain silver fox.
설산 은여우의 털로 만들어졌습니다.
In addition to being extremely rare and expensive,
매우 희귀하고 값비싼 것 외에도,
And it was a fox that the emperor personally hunted
그리고 황제가 직접 사냥한 여우였습니다
e dada à Rong Yu.
e Dada à Rong Yu.
I wouldn't recognize her.
나는 그녀를 알아보지 못할 것입니다.
I don't know what to say.
무슨 말을 해야할지 모르겠습니다.
I'll give you anything you need
네가 필요한 건 뭐든지 줄게
But why would you steal other people's clothes?
그런데 왜 남의 옷을 훔치려고 합니까?
you.
너.
group.
그룹.
I didn't steal.
나는 훔치지 않았습니다.
A Rong Yu me fez mal.
A Rong Yu me fez Mal.
Enough nonsense.
말도 안되는 소리는 충분합니다.
I'm leaving now.
나는 지금 떠난다.
Mr. Rong.
롱 씨.
please don't misunderstand
오해하지 말아주세요
What my daughter just said.
방금 내 딸이 한 말.
I will discipline my children
나는 내 자녀를 징계할 것이다
So I won't bother you.
그러니 나는 당신을 괴롭히지 않을 것입니다.
Clear.
분명한.
miss. He has a kind heart.
놓치다. 그는 친절한 마음을 가지고 있습니다.
General He, don't blame her too much.
장군님, 그녀를 너무 비난하지 마세요.
I will withdraw.
철회하겠습니다.
please.
제발.
- Zong Ming, - Sim.
- 종밍, - 심.
- Escort Mr. Rong to the door. - Yes Master.
- 롱 씨를 문까지 안내하세요. - 알겠습니다.
Mr. Rong.
롱 씨.
Silly girl!
바보 소녀!
Where are you?
어디세요?
Dare to hide.
감히 숨으세요.
Stop hiding.
숨지 마세요.
What a silly girl!
정말 어리석은 소녀입니다!
- Don't run. - Dad, this is a misunderstanding.
- 뛰지 마세요. - 아빠, 이건 오해예요.
Dad, this is a misunderstanding.
아빠, 이건 오해예요.
come over.
이리와.
Kneel down.
에 무릎을 꿇고 앉다.
Stop protecting her!
그녀를 보호하지 마세요!
- Dad - Do you still want to cover for her?
- 아빠 - 아직도 그 사람을 대신하고 싶나요?
- Don't run. - calm.
- 뛰지 마세요. - 침착한.
- stop. - It hurts.
- 멈추다. - 아파요.
- Silly girl. - Stop there.
- 바보 소녀. - 거기 멈춰요.
Better to run.
달리는 것이 좋습니다.
- Run quickly. - stop.
- 빨리 달려. - 멈추다.
It seemed like a scream. it seems
비명을 지르는 것 같았다. 것 같다
- Mercy. - shut up.
- 자비. - 입 다물어.
Dad is ruthless.
아빠는 무자비해요.
Think about it carefully,
잘 생각해보세요,
After returning from Wuhua Mountain
우화산에서 돌아온 후
It's been almost two months.
거의 두 달이 지났습니다.
I have more for you
나는 당신을 위해 더 많은 것을 가지고 있습니다
More in these two months than in the past 16 years.
지난 16년보다 이번 두 달 동안 더 많은 일이 일어났습니다.
look. here.
바라보다. 여기.
here and here.
여기 그리고 여기.
a man who has never been defeated
한 번도 패배한 적이 없는 남자
Not a real man.
진짜 남자가 아닙니다.
This makes sense.
이것은 의미가 있습니다.
hope
희망
I'm going to take the spring exam soon
곧 봄 시험을 치르려고 해요
I can't break my leg now.
이제 다리를 부러뜨릴 수 없습니다.
Then
그 다음에
What are you going to do now?
지금 무엇을 할 예정 이니?
I'm looking for a way.
나는 방법을 찾고 있다.
Judging from his appearance,
그의 외모로 보아,
When he looked at me, his eyes were wide.
그가 나를 보았을 때 그의 눈은 크게 뜨였다.
He is afraid of me.
그는 나를 두려워합니다.
I don't think he is
내 생각엔 그 사람은 아닌 것 같아
Trying to marry me.
나와 결혼하려고 합니다.
Am I wrong?
내가 잘못?
It's obvious that I hate him.
내가 그를 싫어하는 것은 분명하다.
Now there is a misunderstanding.
이제 오해가 생겼습니다.
How did he get it wrong?
그가 어떻게 잘못 생각한 걸까요?
We need to talk.
우리는 이야기를 해야 합니다.
if you go talk to him
가서 그 사람이랑 얘기하면
What do you use a knife for?
칼은 무엇에 사용하나요?
just kidding.
농담이에요.
【Planetarium】
【별자리 투영기】
What does Ms. mean? He wrote that he made her so happy?
Ms.은 무슨 뜻인가요? 그 사람이 그녀를 그렇게 행복하게 만들었다고 썼나요?
She wants to see me.
그녀는 나를 만나고 싶어합니다.
You have to go.
당신은 가야 해요.
In the two months since I returned to the capital,
수도로 돌아온 지 두 달 만에,
You and Heshan
당신과 허산
They are cleaning up something caused by the lady. Hey.
그들은 아주머니가 일으킨 일을 청소하고 있습니다. 여기요.
Just once, Heshan failed to act in time
단 한 번, 허샨은 제때에 행동하지 못했습니다.
Mr. Song reported everything to the government.
송 씨는 모든 것을 정부에 보고했다.
E o old man. He San,
에오 노인네. 허 산,
Climbing walls for no reason.
이유 없이 벽을 오르는 것.
You need to talk reason into her head.
그녀의 머릿속에 이유를 말해야합니다.
[Para Rong Yu]
[파롱 유]
You have a lot to do every day
넌 매일 할 일이 많아
But you still need to pay attention to her.
하지만 여전히 그녀에게 주의를 기울여야 합니다.
What's more, she saved me from danger a few days ago.
게다가 그녀는 며칠 전 나를 위험에서 구해줬어요.
It's my duty to protect her.
그녀를 보호하는 것이 내 의무입니다.
if i can do this in my life
내가 인생에서 이것을 할 수 있다면
let her remain innocent
그녀를 결백하게 놔두세요
I will be very happy.
나는 매우 기쁠 것이다.
Why must she change?
왜 그녀는 변해야 합니까?
It's hard for you and Heshan.
당신과 Heshan에게는 힘든 일입니다.
We are not afraid of hard work,
우리는 힘든 일을 두려워하지 않고,
As long as we can help them.
우리가 그들을 도울 수 있는 한.
I will pack an outfit for the date.
데이트용 옷을 챙겨갈게요.
The Emperor sent new gifts from the Silk Pavilion a few days ago.
황제는 며칠 전 실크 파빌리온에서 새로운 선물을 보냈습니다.
no need.
필요 없음.
Our engagement is not yet complete.
우리의 약혼은 아직 완료되지 않았습니다.
A private meeting would ruin her reputation.
사적인 만남은 그녀의 평판을 망칠 것입니다.
she doesn't understand
그녀는 이해하지 못한다
But I have to behave.
하지만 나는 행동해야 해요.
When I went to Shangzhou last time,
지난번 상저우에 갔을 때
I've offended her too much.
나는 그녀를 너무 많이 화나게했습니다.
I can't make another mistake this time.
이번에는 또 다른 실수를 할 수 없습니다.
She is known as the Overlord of the Capital.
그녀는 수도의 군주로 알려져 있습니다.
But she is still an innocent girl.
하지만 그녀는 여전히 순진한 소녀이다.
Master, I care about you.
선생님, 저는 당신을 걱정합니다.
Avoiding me again.
또 나를 피하는구나.
I know.
알아요.
He is afraid of me.
그는 나를 두려워합니다.
look.
바라보다.
maybe your letter
어쩌면 당신의 편지
Too aggressive
너무 공격적이다
Who is afraid to go out.
밖에 나가는 것을 두려워하는 사람.
Don't forget that idiot young master
그 멍청한 청년 주인님을 잊지 마세요
do lorde Zhongyong
영주 중용을해라
I was worried about your challenge letter not long ago.
얼마 전 당신의 이의제기 편지 때문에 걱정이 됐어요.
But still dare not leave.
하지만 여전히 감히 떠날 수는 없습니다.
He took the bathroom to the bedroom.
그는 화장실을 침실로 가져갔습니다.
what are you waiting for?
무엇을 기다리고 있나요?
Send another letter.
또 다른 편지를 보내세요.
He is a weakling who cannot fight.
그는 싸울 수 없는 약자이다.
Why are you trying to scare him?
왜 그 사람에게 겁을 주려고 하는 거죠?
Be gentle this time
이번에는 부드럽게
And convince him a little bit.
그리고 그 사람을 조금 설득해 보세요.
What? He is a man. Why should I do this?
무엇? 그는 남자입니다. 왜 이 일을 해야 합니까?
Be kind.
친절하게 대해.
let's go.
갑시다.
As the saying goes: "The bright moon is in the willow tree"
'버드나무에 밝은 달이 뜬다' 라는 말이 있듯이
Trading takes place after dark.
거래는 어두워진 후에 이루어집니다.
See you on the bridge tomorrow night?
내일 밤에 다리에서 만나요?
merge?
병합?
Master Rong, I miss you and dream about you
롱 선생님, 당신이 그리워요 그리고 당신에 대한 꿈을 꿔요
crazily
미친듯이
Would you do me the honor of making your acquaintance?
당신과 친분을 쌓는 영광을 저에게 주시겠어요?
teacher.
선생님.
There should be ten, right?
10개는 있어야 겠죠?
I've sent ten letters, right?
나 10통의 편지를 보냈지, 그렇지?
Isn't this too kind?
너무 친절하지 않나요?
I even perfumed the paper.
나는 심지어 종이에 향수를 뿌리기도 했다.
I used all my talents
나는 내 재능을 모두 사용했다.
Write clear invitation verses.
명확한 초대 문구를 작성하세요.
Isn't this sincere enough?
이 정도면 진심 아닌가요?
Maybe Master Rong really has something going on.
어쩌면 Master Rong에게 정말 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지도 모릅니다.
How busy does he have to be?
그 사람은 얼마나 바빠야 합니까?
Go out and talk?
나가서 얘기할까?
He always said he was looking at the stars.
그는 항상 별을 보고 있다고 말했습니다.
Look at the charts during the day and the stars at night.
낮에는 차트를 보고 밤에는 별을 보세요.
I think he's just evading and making excuses.
그냥 회피하고 변명만 하는 것 같아요.
He had no idea what would happen when I lost my cool.
그는 내가 냉정을 잃었을 때 무슨 일이 일어날지 전혀 몰랐습니다.
where are you going?
어디 가세요?
If the mountains don't come to me, I will.
산이 나에게 오지 않으면 내가 올 것이다.
If he doesn't come to me, I'll come to him.
그가 나에게 오지 않으면 내가 그에게 갈 것이다.
I must kill him today.
오늘은 그를 죽여야 해요.
Killing chickens behind the kitchen
부엌 뒤에서 닭 죽이기
And prepare some soup for my dad.
그리고 아빠를 위해 수프를 준비하세요.
Brother, are you here to see the horses too?
형님도 말 보러 오셨나요?
We're here to get the horses.
우리는 말을 얻으러 왔습니다.
After the young lady came back from Wuhua Mountain,
아가씨가 오화산에서 돌아온 뒤
My father kept some fine horses from the Turks,
나의 아버지는 터키산 좋은 말 몇 마리를 기르셨고,
Prepare them to give it to the Lord.
그것을 주님께 드리도록 준비시키십시오.
Today they finally arrived.
오늘 그들은 마침내 도착했습니다.
group.
그룹.
I was wrong.
내가 틀렸어.
I shouldn't ignore him.
나는 그를 무시해서는 안 된다.
However,
하지만,
You and Qiu Ting were almost killed
당신과 Qiu Ting은 거의 죽을 뻔했습니다.
The proud horse of the Rong family
롱 가문의 자랑스러운 말
Dad feels bad.
아빠는 기분이 안 좋아요.
He planned to give the horses to the Rong family.
그는 Rong 가족 에게 말을 줄 계획이었습니다 .
What?
무엇?
They are Turkish horses and can travel thousands of kilometers in a day.
그들은 터키 말이며 하루에 수천 킬로미터를 이동할 수 있습니다.
Do you want Rong Yu to use them to pull the cart?
Rong Yu가 그것들을 사용하여 카트를 끌기를 원하시나요 ?
Might as well leave it to He San.
He San에게 맡기는 것이 나을 수도 있습니다.
if they were no better than horses
만약 그들이 말보다 나을 것이 없다면
We cannot send them as gifts.
우리는 그것들을 선물로 보낼 수 없습니다.
All because of you.
모든게 너 때문이야.
Father and brother.
아버지와 형제.
what are they doing?
그들은 무엇을 하고 있나요?
She looked angrier now.
그녀는 이제 더 화난 것처럼 보였습니다.
nothing.
아무것도 아님.
It’s just that his father is planning to use Turkish horses to compensate Rong Yu
그의 아버지는 Rong Yu에게 보상하기 위해 터키 말을 사용할 계획입니다.
It was originally yours and Jiuling's.
그것은 원래 당신과 Jiuling의 것이었습니다.
- What? - Give him more feed, okay?
- 무엇? - 사료를 더 주세요, 알았죠?
correct.
옳은.
He always wants others to believe him.
그는 항상 다른 사람들이 자신을 믿기를 원합니다.
The Ministry of Justice approved it and he should be there tomorrow.
법무부가 이를 승인했고 그는 내일 그곳에 도착할 것입니다.
Until the spring exam,
봄시험 전까지는
You will report to me daily and read documents.
당신은 매일 나에게 보고하고 문서를 읽을 것입니다.
What?
무엇?
look.
바라보다.
Isn't this a scream?
이건 비명소리 아닌가요?
Yes!
예!
let's go. She is not calm.
갑시다. 그녀는 침착하지 않습니다.
here it is.
여기있어.
Always times.
항상 시간.
Take a look.
구경하다.
Look how shameless you are!
당신이 얼마나 뻔뻔한지보세요!
- correct! - What a abused girl!
- 옳은! - 정말 학대받는 소녀예요!
- keeps coming. - no problem.
- 계속 와요. - 괜찮아요.
I miss her.
나는 그녀를 그리워한다.
You and I must be very close too.
당신과 나도 아주 가까운 사이임에 틀림없어요.
I miss you so much after not seeing you for a few days.
며칠 동안 만나지 못해서 너무 보고 싶어요.
There must be a lot to say after reading the brochure.
브로셔를 읽고 나면 할 말이 많을 것입니다.
We are soul mates, I don't need to pretend.
우리는 소울메이트이기 때문에 그런 척할 필요는 없습니다.
you and me?
너와 나?
When did we become soulmates?
우리는 언제 소울메이트가 되었나요?
When the Star Reacher is ambushed,
스타 리처(Star Reacher)가 매복 공격을 당했을 때,
How you jumped into the rainbow.
어떻게 무지개에 뛰어들었는지.
everyone in the capital
수도에 있는 모든 사람들
They know about your unrequited love for him.
그들은 그에 대한 당신의 짝사랑에 대해 알고 있습니다.
I have seen many ups and downs
우여곡절을 많이 봤습니다
But I praise your affection.
하지만 나는 당신의 애정을 칭찬합니다.
I haven’t solved the sensual painting yet.
아직 감각적인 그림은 못 풀었어요.
How dare you gossip about my feelings for Rong Yu?
어떻게 감히 Rong Yu에 대한 내 감정에 대해 험담을 합니까 ?
I'm going to beat you until you fail to speak!
네가 말을 못 할 때까지 때릴 거야!
OK,
좋아요,
even if i didn't say
내가 말하지 않았더라도
These people will think the same thing.
그 사람들도 같은 생각을 할 것이다.
Is it that obvious?
그렇게 뻔한가요?
You know exactly what happened.
당신은 무슨 일이 일어났는지 정확히 알고 있습니다.
If you want to save someone, save them.
누군가를 구하고 싶다면 저장하세요.
Why hugs and hugs?
왜 포옹하고 포옹합니까?
This is what happened.
이것이 일어난 일입니다.
You are really capable.
당신은 정말 능력이 있습니다.
I want to know which woman in the world
세상에 어떤 여자가 있는지 알고 싶어
He was unwilling to hold Master Rong in his arms.
그는 롱 사부를 품에 안고 싶지 않았습니다.
But you did it,
하지만 당신은 해냈습니다.
And in front of a lot of people.
그리고 많은 사람들 앞에서.
That sight is so exciting
그 광경은 정말 신난다
I want to draw.
나는 그림을 그리고 싶다.
It's all full of love,
온통 사랑으로 가득 차 있고,
Cannot be hidden.
숨길 수 없습니다.
No.
아니요.
If you don't believe it, just let it be.
믿을 수 없다면 그냥 놔두세요.
Now.
지금.
I need to talk to you about something else.
다른 얘기를 좀 해야겠어요.
Sensual paintings.
감각적인 그림.
Do you read so fast?
그렇게 빨리 읽나요?
The next volume is not ready yet.
다음 권은 아직 준비되지 않았습니다.
Wait a moment.
잠시만 기다려주세요.
The sale of these items is not allowed in the capital.
수도에서는 이러한 품목의 판매가 허용되지 않습니다.
Do you print or sell it?
인쇄하거나 판매하시나요?
Confess quickly
빨리 고백해
Otherwise I will beat you.
그렇지 않으면 내가 당신을 이길 것입니다.
I didn't design it and I didn't sell it.
제가 디자인한 것도 아니고 판매한 것도 아닙니다.
So what are you hiding?
그래서 당신은 무엇을 숨기고 있습니까?
anything.
아무것.
This noise.
이 소음.
Is it a fingerprint?
지문인가요?
It's not with me.
나와는 관련이 없습니다.
if you don't admit it
네가 그걸 인정하지 않는다면
- I'll let you see a judge! - No!
- 판사님을 만나보시죠! - 아니요!
That's unfair of you.
그건 불공평해요.
You read it, but you don't want anyone else to read it, do you?
당신은 그것을 읽었지만 다른 사람이 그것을 읽는 것을 원하지 않습니까?
Moreover, Star Lord is not her husband.
게다가 스타로드는 그녀의 남편이 아니다.
Why are you so overprotective?
왜 그렇게 과보호하는 거야?
If you talk nonsense again, I will beat you.
또 헛소리하면 때릴 거야.
here it is.
여기있어.
elder brother.
형.
♫ Dusk as the sun sets♫
♫ 해가 지는 황혼♫
♫I have traveled thousands of miles ♫
♫나는 수천 마일을 여행했어요 ♫
♫ Play the sitar under the moonlight ♫
♫ 달빛 아래서 시타르를 연주해 보세요 ♫
♫ Drinks won’t let me forget ♫
♫ 술은 내가 잊지 못하게 해줄 거예요 ♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫내 소망에 관해 당신에게 편지를 씁니다♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있습니다♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 가장 강한 포도주처럼 ♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 운명에는 탈출구가 없습니다 ♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫돌아보면 기다리고 있는 네가 보여♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫ You turn around silently and close the wedding book♫
♫ 당신은 조용히 돌아서서 결혼식 장부를 덮습니다♫
♫Ask how many stars there are in the sky♫
♫하늘에 별이 몇 개 있는지 물어보세요♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫내 소망에 관해 당신에게 편지를 씁니다♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있습니다♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 가장 강한 포도주처럼 ♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 운명에는 탈출구가 없습니다 ♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫돌아보면 기다리고 있는 네가 보여♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫I play the sitar softly waiting for someone like you♫
♫나는 너 같은 사람을 기다리며 조용히 시타르를 연주한다 ♫
♫In the end you are my inevitable destiny♫
♫결국 당신은 나의 피할 수 없는 운명♫